var questions = [
  {
    question: 'What should the `alt` attribute be?',
    extras: 'question-1',
    correct: 2,
    choices: [
      '`alt="logo"`',
      '`alt="Logo for Ghosts’R’Us"`',
      '`alt="Ghosts’R’Us"`',
      '`alt=""`'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What should the `alt` attribute be?',
    extras: 'question-2',
    correct: 0,
    choices: [
      '`alt="Babs hiding her eyes as a shadow of the bogey-owl follows her"`',
      '`alt="Illustration"`',
      '`alt=""`',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What should the `alt` attribute be?',
    extras: 'question-3',
    correct: 2,
    choices: [
      '`alt="Learn the ways of dragon wrangling"`',
      '`alt="A woodcut of a knight battling an evil dragon"`',
      '`alt=""`',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What should the `alt` attributes be?',
    extras: 'question-4',
    correct: 2,
    choices: [
      '`alt="Ghost"`',
      '`alt="A ghost looking spookily onwards"`',
      '`alt=""`',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What should the `alt` attribute be?',
    extras: 'question-5',
    correct: 2,
    choices: [
      '`alt="Monsters of the air and deep leaving the port of Palos, they had been constantly on the watch"`',
      '`alt="All the monsters"`',
      '`alt=""`',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What should the `alt` attribute be?',
    extras: 'question-6',
    correct: 0,
    choices: [
      '`alt="Monsters of the air and deep leaving the port of Palos, they had been constantly on the watch"`',
      '`alt="All the monsters"`',
      '`alt=""`',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What should the `alt` attribute be?',
    extras: 'question-7',
    correct: 2,
    choices: [
      '`alt="Company logo"`',
      '`alt="Company name in hairy monster text"`',
      '`alt="Harry Monster’s Emporium for Hairy Monsters"`',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What should the `alt` attribute be?',
    extras: 'question-8',
    correct: 0,
    choices: [
      '`alt="Monster attacks — 1775: 1.8M, 1775: 2.0M, 1777: 2.4M, 1778: 3.1M, 1779: 3.8M"`',
      '`alt="A bar graph denoting the a steady increase in monster attacks since 1775"`',
      '`alt=""`',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What should the `alt` attribute be?',
    extras: 'question-9',
    correct: 1,
    choices: [
      '`alt="Monster attacks — 1775: 1.8M, 1775: 2.0M, 1777: 2.4M, 1778: 3.1M, 1779: 3.8M"`',
      '`alt="A bar graph denoting the a steady increase in monster attacks since 1775"`',
      '`alt=""`',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What should the `alt` attribute be?',
    extras: 'question-10',
    correct: 2,
    choices: [
      '`alt="The Sea Fairies by Frank L. Baum"`',
      '`alt=""`',
      'No `alt` — background images are purely decoration',
    ]
  }
];

MultipleChoice(ActivityRunner(), questions);
